## **SUGANDHA RAO**

7 Gate Court, Gateway, Weybridge, KT13 8NW, UK raosugandha12@gmail.com

## SUMMARY

Highly self-motivated and goal oriented professional with 5+ years of experience in array of fields ranging from Content management | Knowledge management to Web development. I have 2 years of experience in developing mobile responsive sites with web applications like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Holds valid UK work permit (valid until May 2022)

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Front-End: CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, JavaScript, nodeJs, Git, GitHub, BEM, NPM and mobile first responsive
- Web Tools: Brackets, Adobe Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Sublime and Notepad++
- Application Software: MS Office Suite
- Experience in coding and development for content-driven large-scale sites
- In-depth knowledge of coding best practices, testing cross-platform, cross-browser compatibility, web development tools
- Experience designing and building HTML email marketing newsletters
- Strong understanding of content management systems
- Content Management Systems: SharePoint 2010, SharePoint 2013, WordPress

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **RESEARCH ANALYST**

Deloitte, India

**January 2016 to June 2017** Hyderabad, India

Provided web content management support for business need for all functions (Audit, Advisory, Consulting and Tax) within Deloitte by creating, improving and maintaining content on websites and social media channels like yammer.

- Converted Photoshop layouts to mobile responsive web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- · Interpreted and executed website designs as requested by clients
- Create browser and platform compatible CSS codes/ style sheets
- Converted PSD to HTML email templates
- Write web pages using a combination of markup languages and testing cross-platform, cross-browser compatibility

#### **EXECUTIVE KNOWLEDGE MANAGEMENT**

March 2010 to November 2013

Nagarro Software, India

Gurgaon, India

- Providing end to end support in managing knowledge capture, knowledge reuse. Support members of the Sales /Proposal team in a knowledge worker capacity by capturing sections of proposal documents, deliverable, and success stories
- Training and guiding new team members which includes assigning client requests, checking the quality of deliverable

# **EDUCATION**

**POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN DATA ANALYTIC** from Indian Institute of Information Technology, Bangalore, India (2017-2018). **Specialization:** Analytic with R

**MASTERS IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (MBA)** from the Ansal Institute of Technology, India. (2008-2010). **Specialization:** Human Resource

**BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY(WITH HONORS)(B.TECH)** from Kurukshetra University, India (2003 – 2007). **Specialization:** Biotechnology